https://onlynaturalinc.com/privacy-notice/

Only naturalYou have no items in your shopping cart. My CartCheckoutSign InRegisterHomeFAQsShareFind a store
Home    Privacy NoticePrivacy Notice
PRIVACY POLICYOnly Natural, Inc. does not sell, rent or trade your personal information to third parties. Only Natural, Inc. does not knowingly collect information online from children under 13. If you have questions about Only Natural, Inc.'s Privacy Policy, contact us by: Phone: (516) 897-7001 E-mail: info@onlyanturalinc.com Postal mail: Only Natural, Inc. 3580 Oceanside Road, Unit #5, Oceanside, NY  11572.  Our Privacy Commitment to Our Customers: We value the relationship we have with our customers and are committed to responsible information-handling practices. We take great care in safeguarding your personal information and in complying with all applicable federal and state privacy laws and our own internal standards and best practices. Only Natural IncIs committed to the protection of your privacy. We have created this privacy statement in order to fully describe our Privacy Policy. This Privacy and Security Policy applies to all of the information that we receive from people like you, who contact our Web site at: Web site : https://onlynaturalinc.com  Email: sales@onlynaturalinc.comSecurity:Only Natural Inc. uses the latest encryption technology and other methods to protect any personal information. We recommend that you use version 4.0 or higher for either Microsoft Internet Explorer or Netscape Communicator/Navigator for your web browser. If you are using one of these browsers (and are not using a proxy server) all transactions are fully encrypted and secure via Secure Sockets Layer (SSL).Use a browser, such as Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer, that supports SSL. These browsers show a symbol near the bottom of the window ( status bar ) such as a lock or key, when you are on a site that uses SSL, and the address window at the top of the browser changes from http:// to https://.When you use the web site some basic general information is collected. Cookies are also used to distinguish your shopping cart session and to help us determine the various services you use, the support you may need, and to help us detect and solve any problems with our servers or other needs that you may have when using our web site.Sensitive Information:When you contact us and provide information, some connection information may be used to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our web site. Like the majority of  Web site servers we use log files. These log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring page, platform type, date/time stamp. IP addresses, browser type, etc., are not linked to personally identifiable information. Only Natural Inc.will never sell, rent or otherwise distribute your e-mail address to any other company or organization. During your shopping you will be asked to provide us with some sensitive information (like your name, contact phone number and e-mail address) and financial information (like your credit card number, credit card billing address and credit card expiration date) This information is needed when you place an online order with Only Natural Inc. The information we collect from you is used only for the purpose of processing your order, billing you for products and services, servicing your account and shipping your order, and is kept secure and confidential.Information from Children:This site does not knowingly solicit, target or sell any products or services to children under the age of 13 years, nor does it specifically target any information towards children. We do not collect information from any person we actually know is under the age of 13, that would make that child personally identifiable.This site does not knowingly sell any products or services to children under the age of 18 years. We advise any parent that feel that anything about this site is inappropriate for their child, to monitor their child's use of this site as they would all other Internet usage. Only Natural always welcome your input and/or comments. Please feel free to contact us any time.Use of Cookies : Every time you visit our web site your browser will be required to accept new cookies; a cookie is a small text file that is used by your browser to uniquely identify your shopping cart order to our web server every time you are placing any orders on our web site.                                                  Thank you                              ManagementBrowse our products Select CategoryProducts of the MonthComplete HealthHealth SupportMen’s HealthWomen’s HealthWeight Management, Cleanse and DetoxVegetarian/ KosherCardiovascular HealthMood/Sleep & Brain HealthImmune/Bone & Joint HealthAnti-Aging/ Health & BeautySuper Fruits & AntioxidantsCapsulesLiquidsPowdersTabletsTeasVegetable CapsulesGel CapsOrganic Juices
GoPersonal analysisWhat supplements are right for you? Select sexFemaleMale
Select age0- 1718-5050+ View Recommended Products
Follow @OnlyNaturalInc
Best Sellers New Products Products Healthy News About Contact FAQs Disclaimer Products of the Month Complete Health Health Support Men’s Health Women’s Health Weight Management, Cleanse and Detox Vegetarian/ Kosher Cardiovascular Health Mood/Sleep & Brain Health Immune/Bone & Joint HealthAnti-Aging/ Health & Beauty Super Fruits & Antioxidants Capsules Liquids Powders Tablets Teas Vegetable Capsules Gel Caps Organic Juices Only Natural Inc. 3580 Oceanside Road; Unit #5 Oceanside, NY
11572 Ph: 1-516-897-7001 Fax: 1-516-897-9332
†These statements have not been evaluated by the FDA. These products are not intended to diagnose, treat, cure or prevent any disease. Policies   |   Privacy Notice
|   Conditions of Use
|   Catalog Sitemap
|   Products Sitemap
Copyright © 2020 Only Natural Inc. All rights reserved
Onlynaturalinc.com Ecommerce Design by Blue Fountain Media
